<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Twizted Myrtle</title>
    <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Twizted Myrtle</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>You Complete Me</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/you-complete-me.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/you-complete-me.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Romantic words that make your heart flutter, and arguably, the biggest crock of shit ever vocalized as the Holy Grail in the name of love! So what do these words really mean? Let the indulgence begin …&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twizted New Year</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/twizted-new-year.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/twizted-new-year.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Every year we wish for peace and happiness. So why have we not attained it yet? We can achieve the unthinkable like landing man on the moon when we have collective undeterred resolve. And yet, peace continues to evade us.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Giving</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/the-art-of-giving.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/the-art-of-giving.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Why do we give gifts? Consciously or sub-consciously and to varying degrees, we use gifts as a way to further our agenda – impress or pacify someone, fulfill an obligation, win them over, one-up the recipient or our competition, score points , call in a favor in the future, use as a tool for guilt and manipulation, earn bragging rights or boost our own ego. When we give with ulterior motives, agenda or expectations, a gift turns into a contract.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Fashion Is Murder</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/when-fashion-is-murder.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/when-fashion-is-murder.html.html</guid>
      <description>Compassionate or Murderer - What statement do your fashion choices make about you?
Our desire for comfort and to look cool in fur coats, leather handbags and snakeskin shoes comes at an unthinkable price; cows, dogs and cats are amongst the many animals that are subjected to heart wrenching cruelty. How is that cool? What really happens behind the scenes? How can India be the biggest supplier of cows for the leather industry when they consider cows to be sacred?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>thankyou</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/thankyou.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2016 23:32:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/thankyou.html</guid>
      <description>    Mahalo      Thank you for you interest. I&#39;ll be in touch soon. If I&#39;m out in the boonies somewhere photographing some cool shit, then it may take me a little longer. Talk soon :)                 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>privacy</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/privacy.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2016 23:32:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/privacy.html</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy  Updated: Jan 2018
Product Orders A variety of personal information is collected for each product order. This includes: your name, address, email and phone number. This information is shared with our print fulfillment vendors to ensure delivery of your order. Email is used to communicate with you about your order and to manage our relationship. When you place an order, you may be added to the Smashup newsletter; you can unsubscribe at any time using the unsubscribe link or shoot an email to hello@twiztedmyrtle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>error</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/error.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2016 23:32:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/error.html</guid>
      <description>$(document).ready(function() { // Add the missing url to the text $(&#34;#url&#34;).text(window.location.pathname); // Fix the css locations dynamically $(&#34;head link&#34;).each(function() { for (var i=0; iSorry, the page  could not be found on this server. Go back home. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>copyright</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/terms-of-use.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2016 23:31:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/terms-of-use.html</guid>
      <description>Terms of Use  Legal mumbo-jumbo is a necessary evil. Or so they say. On a positive note, it makes for really good bedtime reading. It may not be as simple as Dr. Seuss, but it’s pretty darn close. Here goes the most legible fine print ... By accessing this site, you agree to be bound by all terms set forth below. If you do not agree to all of the terms, please exit, depart, make a break, hit the road, move on, scram and abandon the website now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>prints</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/bazaar.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 17:30:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/bazaar.html</guid>
      <description>Art should disturb the comfortable &amp;amp; comfort the disturbed    Art that only a few privileged can own through manufactured demand to drive up the commercial value is manipulative. It promotes concepts of scarcity and superiority to pander to our fragile egos. For Twizted Myrtle to offer limited edition would simply be disingenuous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>giving back</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/giving-back.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 17:30:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/giving-back.html</guid>
      <description>Be a drop in the ocean  We are bombarded with a plethora of issues that tug at our hearts. They can make us feel sad, angry, fearful, and even overwhelmed. It can be paralyzing. After all, one person certainly can’t lend their help to all of these causes, right? But one person doesn’t have to solve all problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Legalize or Not to Legalize Marijuana, with Doug Coleman, Special Agent at Drug Enforcement Agency</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/to-legalize-or-not-to-legalize-marijuana-with-doug-coleman-special-agent-at-drug-enforcement-agency.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/to-legalize-or-not-to-legalize-marijuana-with-doug-coleman-special-agent-at-drug-enforcement-agency.html.html</guid>
      <description>Doug Coleman is a 25-year veteran and Special Agent for DEA, in charge of the Phoenix Field Division, and Michael Pooley, Metro Operations Lieutenant for Tempe Police Department. As a border state, Arizona plays a vital role in the infiltration and distribution of drugs to the rest of our country. We engage in a riveting conversation about all things drugs, no holds barred!
Do DEA agents have any compassion for drug dealers and the choices they make as a result of their circumstances?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>contact</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/contact.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 00:33:53 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/contact.html</guid>
      <description>Looking for a different perspective?      Bonjour&amp;nbsp; Bonjour Booyakasha Marhaba Ciao Kon’nichiwa Hola Aloha Hallo Namaste Zdravstvuyte Nin hao    &amp;nbsp; Twizted! My name is . I&#39;m contacting you because Yoda sent me&amp;nbsp; Yoda sent me I have a custom photography request I want to support your wickedly uncomfortable work I&#39;d like you to write about a topic that&#39;s dear to me I&#39;d like to interview you I just dig your work   .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>scars project</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/scars-project.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 00:29:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/scars-project.html</guid>
      <description>7.2 Billionhuman souls ALL HAVE SCARS!           Empowering Scars  Pain is universal and timeless. No one is immune, regardless of age, race, religion, sex, color, nationality, culture, education or financial status. That’s life. And yet, there is a strong unhealthy tendency, across the globe, to not discuss our pain; reasons include cultural taboo, judgment, shame, guilt and perception.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chasing Unhappiness</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/chasing-unhappiness.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/chasing-unhappiness.html.html</guid>
      <description>While lazing around on a Sunday afternoon, my mind, like most entrepreneurs, was working. In doing so, I asked myself one question – The day you reach the heights of success you’ve always envisioned for your company (my BHAG – Big Hairy Audacious Goal), how will you feel that day? The answer surprised me – Emptiness.
While I would feel a strong sense of accomplishment, proud of our team and what we built together, I also became acutely aware that it would be a shallow experience; I would feel a deep sense of emptiness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Louie Psihoyos, Academy Award Winning Director, Creates the Tipping Point to Change the World!</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/how-louie-psihoyos-academy-award-winning-director-creates-the-tipping-point-to-change-the-world.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/how-louie-psihoyos-academy-award-winning-director-creates-the-tipping-point-to-change-the-world.html.html</guid>
      <description>Louie Psihoyos is an Academy Award Winning Director, and Founder/CEO of Oceanic Preservation Society. With a three day crash course in film making, it&amp;rsquo;s ironic that Louie&amp;rsquo;s first documentary film, The Cove, won over 100 awards including the Academy Award. How is this even possible? What advice did Steven Spielberg give him? Did he listen? Louie discusses how covert operations allowed him to capture one of the most poignant and chilling scenes in The Cove, where elders in Taiji, Japan, share how they used to kill Blue Whales prior to wreaking havoc on dolphins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Behind the Scenes with Nyla, an Extraordinaire Burlesque Stripper</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/behind-the-scenes-with-nyla-an-extraordinaire-burlesque-stripper.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/behind-the-scenes-with-nyla-an-extraordinaire-burlesque-stripper.html.html</guid>
      <description>What does a man REALLY want when he goes to a strip club? Nyla, founder of Violet Flame Studios, and an extraordinaire Burlesque Stripper, takes us behind the scenes and unveils how strip clubs work, stripper code of ethics and the art of seduction. But how did she make the big leap from being a dancer to a stripper? What was it like when she got topless for the first time?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pt 2 - Adam Sud, Former Addict&#39;s Perspective on How to Get Through to an Addict and The War on Drugs</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-2---adam-sud-former-addicts-perspective-on-how-to-get-through-to-an-addict-and-the-war-on-drugs.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-2---adam-sud-former-addicts-perspective-on-how-to-get-through-to-an-addict-and-the-war-on-drugs.html.html</guid>
      <description>Adam Sud is the son of one of the founding investors of Whole Foods. Despite having all the right ingredients in life, Adam’s life was on the fastest route to self destruction. But Adam took charge and reversed his Type 2 Diabetes, lost 150lbs, kicked his addiction to Adderall and Food … and transformed his life … physically, as well as emotionally. In our last episode, Adam shared the journey of his transformation and what he lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pt 1 - How Adam Sud Reversed His Diabetes, Lost 150 lbs, Kicked His Food/Rx Addiction and Transformed His Life</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-1---how-adam-sud-reversed-his-diabetes-lost-150-lbs-kicked-his-food/rx-addiction-and-transformed-his-life.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-1---how-adam-sud-reversed-his-diabetes-lost-150-lbs-kicked-his-food/rx-addiction-and-transformed-his-life.html.html</guid>
      <description>Adam Sud is the son of founding investor of Whole Foods. Despite having access to all the right ingredients in life, Adam found himself addicted to prescription drugs, overweight at 300 lbs, diagnosed with Type 2 Diabetes, low self esteem, wrapped in depression and anger, out of cash, unemployed and primed to live on the streets? How? And why? Adam went from a journey of self-destruction to inspiring self-transformation. Adam reversed his Type 2 Diabetes, lost 150 lbs, gained his self esteem and emotional health back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life After “The Last Letter” by Marc Lee, an American Decorated Fallen Hero</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/life-after-the-last-letter-by-marc-lee-an-american-decorated-fallen-hero.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/life-after-the-last-letter-by-marc-lee-an-american-decorated-fallen-hero.html.html</guid>
      <description>Knock. Knock. Your son, Marc Lee, has been killed in action. As a parent, losing your child is the most painful, heart wrenching and unnatural thing to experience. How do you even process this? How do you deal with such depths of pain and grief? Can you ever heal from such a devastating loss? How do you go on? We talk to Debbie Lee, Marc’s Mom, to discuss this difficult and inspiring journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pt 2 - ISIS &amp; Mind Control: Looking at Suicide Bombers Through a Different Lens</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-2---isis--mind-control-looking-at-suicide-bombers-through-a-different-lens.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-2---isis--mind-control-looking-at-suicide-bombers-through-a-different-lens.html.html</guid>
      <description>Are suicide bombers and members of terrorist groups like ISIS and Al Qaeda demons or are they victims themselves? What does the future hold for young children who have been brainswashed by ISIS? Can and how can people that have been in cult groups for decades be deprogrammed successfully? Will Tom Cruise ever be able to get out of Scientology? Rick Ross, an expert on destructive cults, shares valuable insights into this other world and the process of deprogramming minds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pt 1 - Can Anyone Succumb to Cults and Brainwashing?</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-1---can-anyone-succumb-to-cults-and-brainwashing.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-1---can-anyone-succumb-to-cults-and-brainwashing.html.html</guid>
      <description>Rick Ross is the founder and Executive Director of The Cult Education Institute. He is an internationally known expert on destructive cults, controversial groups and movements. Rick helps us understand if there is a particular profile of people that are more susceptible to cults. How does a cult leader disable our ability to think independently and rationally? What are the exit costs of leaving a cult group? How is Catholicism or Mormonism different from Scientology?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Real Truth Behind Men, Sex and How They Think</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/the-real-truth-behind-men-sex-and-how-they-think.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/the-real-truth-behind-men-sex-and-how-they-think.html.html</guid>
      <description>Vince Kelvin is a famous seduction coach. As a pick up artist, he teaches men how to seduce women and get them in the sack. Sickening, right? Or so it would seem at first glance. Vince opens up about his own personal journey into how be became a pick up artist. His &amp;ldquo;artistry&amp;rdquo; was featured in Lisa Ling&amp;rsquo;s documentary &amp;ldquo;This Is Life&amp;rdquo; on CNN. How does he feel about love, marriage and relationships?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pratham USA, Breaking The Cycle of Poverty and Illiteracy in India</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pratham-usa-breaking-the-cycle-of-poverty-and-illiteracy-in-india.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pratham-usa-breaking-the-cycle-of-poverty-and-illiteracy-in-india.html.html</guid>
      <description>Meet Amit Shah. Education and poverty strike a very personal chord for him. His passion for education turned into action when he got involved with Pratham USA, as a Board Member. Pratham is a non profit organization that strives to educate 200 million children in India that currently cannot read or write. How is that even possible when India boasts 96% enrollment of children in schools? Amit shares his experiences and insights in the lives of some of the children from low income families – what their daily lives look like, daily struggles, their dreams and aspirations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time to Reconsider &#39;Stranger Danger&#39; Teachings and Rethink Concept of Trust</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/time-to-reconsider-stranger-danger-teachings-and-rethink-concept-of-trust.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/time-to-reconsider-stranger-danger-teachings-and-rethink-concept-of-trust.html.html</guid>
      <description>Kids are sexually abused mostly by people in our trusted circle - friends, relatives, teachers and priests. So isn&amp;rsquo;t it time to reconsider &amp;ldquo;Stranger Danger?&amp;rdquo; If we can&amp;rsquo;t trust our family and friends, then who can we trust? Michael Pooley, Lieutenant and PIO at Tempe Police Department, and Rachel Lutowsky, Founder of Dynamic Leadership, and parents, share new and noteworthy insights on what to teach your children so they don&amp;rsquo;t become victims.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Divorce or Stay Unhappily Married for Kids, Society and Culture?</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/divorce-or-stay-unhappily-married-for-kids-society-and-culture.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/divorce-or-stay-unhappily-married-for-kids-society-and-culture.html.html</guid>
      <description>How many unhappy people do you know that stay married for the sake of their kids? Or because even thinking of divorce is taboo in your culture? Should you dare? Does divorce make you a selfish person? Nitin, Indian, was married for 18 years. He shares what he experienced in his marriage, why he considered divorce and how that has impacted his son.
Listen to Show

Resources -
 What You Don&amp;rsquo;t Know About Marriage The inconvenient truth about love - and divorce -  Four Patterns That Predict Divorce (part 1) The Impact of Divorce on Children Deciding to Divorce?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pt 2 - Racing Extinction - Why The Time to Act Is NOW!</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-2---racing-extinction---why-the-time-to-act-is-now.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-2---racing-extinction---why-the-time-to-act-is-now.html.html</guid>
      <description>Shawn Heinrichs - Our conversation continues with Shawn, an Emmy Winning Award Winning Cinematographer, artist, photographer and marine conservationist. It&amp;rsquo;s an awakening, inspiring &amp;amp; intellectually stimulating conversation. Why do people choose to believe that they, as one person, cannot make a difference? Why is the fishing industry knowingly leading creatures to extinction and the death of their livelihood? What does Shawn think of humanity? And behind the scenes on some of the moments showcased in the documentary film, Racing Extinction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pt 1 - Can One Person Change The World?</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-1---can-one-person-change-the-world.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-1---can-one-person-change-the-world.html.html</guid>
      <description>Shawn Heinrichs, an Emmy Award Winning Cinematographer, artist, photographer, and Shark and Manta Ray Defender. Or, more accurately, a Real Life Avenger! Shawn’s incredibly moving work was recently featured in the documentary film, Racing Extinction. But what inspired him to transform his life from corporate America to dedicating and risking his life to save Sharks and Manta Rays? Can one man really change the world?
Listen to Show

Resources -</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to stop living in fear? - Joe Bailey, psychologist, author and speaker</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/how-to-stop-living-in-fear---joe-bailey-psychologist-author-and-speaker.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/how-to-stop-living-in-fear---joe-bailey-psychologist-author-and-speaker.html.html</guid>
      <description>Do you live everyday in fear and anxiety? Does media play a role in the fear with which we live our lives? ISIS. Ebola. Earthquake … the list goes on. How about living in fear due to our own personal experiences and thoughts? Or Donald Trump (and Cruz)? Joe Bailey, psychologist, author and speaker, discuss where fear comes from, why we respond to it and how we can fearproof our lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Do Pakistanis and Indians hate each other?</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/why-do-pakistanis-and-indians-hate-each-other.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/why-do-pakistanis-and-indians-hate-each-other.html.html</guid>
      <description>Why do Pakistanis and Indians hate each other? How does a child pick up on these social and historical cues? Personally, I hated Pakistanis as I was growing up. Do we have good reason to hate each other? What role does Patriotism and cricket play in fueling this hatred? Mustapha, Pakistani, who married an Indian girl, shares his experiences and insight into this issue.
Listen to Show

Resources
 India - Pakistan Relations India - Pakistan Cricket Rivalry A rivalry that threatens the world India-Pakistan Relations: A Destructive Equilibrium Movie - Gandhi  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How NOT to become a victim to your financial advisor with Tigran</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/how-not-to-become-a-victim-to-your-financial-advisor-with-tigran.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/how-not-to-become-a-victim-to-your-financial-advisor-with-tigran.html.html</guid>
      <description>Ever had a bad experience with a financial advisor or know someone who did? Are you afraid of being a victim to these shady advisors? My financial advisor, and friend, certainly helped me lose thousands of dollars. Sadly, this is a fairly common occurrence. Are you trying to get back in the game, but don&amp;rsquo;t know how? Tigran from Hatton Consulting shares insights into the financial industry so you can avoid the pitfalls and get back in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Growing up Black in Chicago with Gina</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/growing-up-black-in-chicago-with-gina.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/growing-up-black-in-chicago-with-gina.html.html</guid>
      <description>Does every Black person experience racial discrimination? Do we need more Black role models? Why do kids wear their pants down? We discuss this and all things Black with Gina who grew up in Chicago in the 1970s.
Listen to Show</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pt 2 - How being an entrepreneur can impact personal relationships with Josh Carroll</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-2---how-being-an-entrepreneur-can-impact-personal-relationships-with-josh-carroll.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-2---how-being-an-entrepreneur-can-impact-personal-relationships-with-josh-carroll.html.html</guid>
      <description>Being an entrepreneur sounds glamorous. But there is a dark underbelly to being a business owner. Josh Carroll, COO &amp;amp; Co-Founder of endsight, shares raw insights into how his entrepreneurial journey impacted his relationship with his wife. Their glamorous life had it all – bankruptcy, post partum depression, fights, dysfunctional love, bitterness and so much more. How did they sort through so much baggage?
Listen to Show</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pt 1 - What it&#39;s REALLY like to be an entrepreneur with Josh Carroll</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-1---what-its-really-like-to-be-an-entrepreneur-with-josh-carroll.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-1---what-its-really-like-to-be-an-entrepreneur-with-josh-carroll.html.html</guid>
      <description>Rarely do you hear true and uncensored stories about what it&amp;rsquo;s REALLY like to be an entrepreneur. To most, owning your own company means you&amp;rsquo;re rolling in a pile of Benjamins and life is peachy. Josh Carroll, COO &amp;amp; Co-Founder of endsight, shares openly and with refreshing honesty about the “real” story behind his entrepreneurial success.
Listen to Show

Resources -
 Inc. Article - The Psychological Price of Entrepreneurship  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India’s obsession with white skin</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/indias-obsession-with-white-skin.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/indias-obsession-with-white-skin.html.html</guid>
      <description>You think America has problems with skin color? Try India! Did you know that India is obsessed with white skin. What are the implications of this unhealthy desire for fair skin? How does this translate into society … our thoughts, self worth and interactions? We explore this topic in depth with Suhrid Ganguly, a Bengali, who has a darker skin complexion.
Listen to Show

Resources -
 Doll Test Video Dark Girls Documentary BBC - “Racist” Thailand skin-whitening advert is withdrawn  Manipulative messages by Fair and Lovely Commercial  Bollywood Actresses like Priyanka Chopra that have undergone skin lightening treatment BBC - Africa, where black is not really beautiful When Black Teens get real about America’s love of light skin BBC - #unfairandlovely: A new social campaign celebrates dark skin   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sexual Advances in Business</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/sexual-advances-in-business.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/sexual-advances-in-business.html.html</guid>
      <description>As a working woman, do you struggle with men hitting on you in business settings? Have you figured out how to handle these unwanted sexual advances, while being taken seriously for your work? Rachel Lutowsky, founder of Dynamic Leadership Solutions, shares some of her undesired experiences and what she’s learned from them.
As a working man, you may also want to tune in to listen to what women experience in the workplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do you know you’re gay?</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/how-do-you-know-youre-gay.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/how-do-you-know-youre-gay.html.html</guid>
      <description>Jeffrey Hattrick was born in a conservative Catholic family. He found himself attracted to men. Oh Boy! So how did his parents react when a love letter he wrote to his man crush fell out of his bag? How did he handle being shoved in trash cans in school? Is it okay to call someone gay, queer or fag? Do gay people have the desire to have children? How do gay people have sex?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Len’s heart attack “woke” him up from a life of quiet desperation</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/how-lens-heart-attack-woke-him-up-from-a-life-of-quiet-desperation.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/how-lens-heart-attack-woke-him-up-from-a-life-of-quiet-desperation.html.html</guid>
      <description>Are you living a life of quiet desperation? You know you’re not happy, but don’t know how to get out of it? Len Gutman knows what that’s like. It took a heart attack to wake him up and change the course of his life. His journey led him to discovering true happiness.
Here’s how he did it - Listen to Show

Resources -
 American Heart Association - www.heart.org Heart Attack Support Group - Under 55 heartattack Calcium Test - Coronary Calcium Scan Book - How to find fulfilling work, Roman Krznaric Book - Your money or your life, Vicki Robin and Joe Dominguez  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sara’s journey of sexual abuse, self-injury and drug addiction</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/saras-journey-of-sexual-abuse-self-injury-and-drug-addiction.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/saras-journey-of-sexual-abuse-self-injury-and-drug-addiction.html.html</guid>
      <description>Meet Sara. It would be fair to say that she&amp;rsquo;s been through hell and back. Sara sheds light on how her perpetrator groomed her for one year to become a victim of sexual abuse. How did he get in her mind? What drove her to cut her body with a razor and become addicted to it? How did she get introduced to drugs?
Her reasons were profound! She left me speechless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Majestic Close Encounter</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/a-majestic-close-encounter.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/a-majestic-close-encounter.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Whales are majestic creatures that symbolize freedom. They can make hearts palpitate with giddiness and excitement like teenage romance. So imagine the inner screams when the Captain radioed our Zodiac driver, Christophe, that there is a whale by the ship and is putting on quite the show. Okay, let&amp;rsquo;s back up a little.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decision to ban India&#39;s Daughter</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/decision-to-ban-indias-daughter.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/decision-to-ban-indias-daughter.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Outcry over the documentary, India&amp;rsquo;s daughter, led to a swift response by the government. The government and parts of the community that supported the decision to ban the documentary is very telling of the Indian mentality  and is worth a closer look.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experiencing Aurora Borealis</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/experiencing-aurora-borealis.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/experiencing-aurora-borealis.html.html</guid>
      <description>Last year, the temptation to see Aurora Borealis grew beyond being a number on my bucket list. I could not resist anymore. So I booked my trip to Iceland for two weeks in December. My excitement came crashing down when my friend educated me that seeing Aurora Borealis is not guaranteed. It&amp;rsquo;s a matter of right weather conditions and location within the country. So off I went to Iceland, with more realistic expectations while hoping to get lucky.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspirational Traveling Mom</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/inspirational-traveling-mom.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/inspirational-traveling-mom.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;New Year&amp;rsquo;s Resolutions are a running joke. They fizzle away by mid-February each year. And yet, we keep repeating the cycle. We have good reasons like our husband, wife, children, job, money and time that keep getting in the way. But the truth is they are not our reasons; they are our excuses.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three hardest words to say</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/three-hardest-words-to-say.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/three-hardest-words-to-say.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Several years ago, if you told me to say &amp;ldquo;I love you&amp;rdquo; to my parents or siblings, I would have laughed and brushed you off. The mere thought of verbalizing such emotional words that made me feel so exposed and vulnerable  was screechingly uncomfortable. We all knew that we loved and cared for each other deeply; but we never actually uttered those three tough words. Never!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iceland, my worst nightmare transformed</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/iceland-my-worst-nightmare-transformed.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/iceland-my-worst-nightmare-transformed.html.html</guid>
      <description>Iceland is unique, complex and intriguing. The island is transforming and evolving in real time since it is geologically active. It is a land of many volcanoes, geysers, geothermal springs, black sand beach , moss and lava fields, mountains, glaciers, lakes, fjords and aurora borealis. I was sold. So I booked a 14-day trip for December, which included a 7-day photo tour with the talented photographer, Iurie Belegurschi. As December approached, I was hardly able to contain my excitement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons learned in 2014</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/lessons-learned-in-2014.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/lessons-learned-in-2014.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just as every book has an end, I conclude each year of my life by reflecting on the big lessons learned that year. In this process, one thing has been consistent since I was thirteen. Each year I look back and realize  how ignorant, immature and daft I was the year prior. In that respect, I love growing old and hopefully a penny wiser. Click below to read the full article:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rethink Respect  |  7 lessons learned from celebrity rapists</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/rethink-respect----7-lessons-learned-from-celebrity-rapists.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/rethink-respect----7-lessons-learned-from-celebrity-rapists.html.html</guid>
      <description>Could Bill Cosby, the most respected family man and Father of America have raped 15 women and counting? That just cannot be. Right? Parents and children equally looked up to him; parents wanted to emulate him and children wanted a father like him. He was wise, funny, educated, understanding, and just plain cool! He was well respected, both as Bill Cosby and as Dr. Huxtable. And that&amp;rsquo;s exactly where it all goes wrong — Respect and Reputation!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First timers guide to Cruise Vacations</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/first-timers-guide-to-cruise-vacations.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/first-timers-guide-to-cruise-vacations.html.html</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve traveled the world by plane, train, bus and car, but never a cruise. The concept of being stuck in a finite amount of space never seemed appealing to me. Still, I wanted to experience it first hand and decide how I really felt about cruise vacations. So in July 2010, I booked a 7 day Mexican Riviera Cruise on the Royal Caribbean, Mariner of the Seas, for our family vacation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coach Needs Coaching In Customer Service!</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/coach-needs-coaching-in-customer-service.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/coach-needs-coaching-in-customer-service.html.html</guid>
      <description>This story makes my blood boil on many levels – as an entrepreneur, as someone who has been on both sides of customer service, as a daughter and as a person. How does spilling a drink on the floor, a trivial event, translate into the most heinous crime of this century? Assistant manager leads her posse by example – arrogance, ego, disrespect and lack of common courtesy. But was this an isolated incident?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I was high ... on speed!</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/i-was-high-...-on-speed.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/i-was-high-...-on-speed.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was a beautiful morning on Dec 7&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt;, 2012 and I was headed out for &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bondurant.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bondurant High Performance Driving School&lt;/a&gt;. The wait for this day had been too long. I had finally signed up for their one-day course which was jam-packed with learning driving maneuvers, techniques and track time. I was super excited, nervous and slightly intimidated. But mostly, I could not contain myself!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women want equality. But only when we want it.</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/women-want-equality.-but-only-when-we-want-it..html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/women-want-equality.-but-only-when-we-want-it..html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Consider a business lunch meeting, date night or just hanging out with friends. Waiter brings the check and typically drops it off closer to the man. Ignoring that gender bias for a hot second, who do you think should pay?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Human Zoo</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/the-human-zoo.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/the-human-zoo.html.html</guid>
      <description>After my experience at The Tiger Kingdom, I was on my way to the next hot spot – The Long Neck Tribe Village in Chiang Mai, Thailand, which came with high recommendations. My expectation was that I was going to be able to visit, interact and learn about The Long Neck Tribe people, culture and their way of life, with authenticity. Little did I know, I was actually visiting a human zoo, where The Long Neck Tribe people were on display for me to gawk at.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cab tales from the front seat</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/cab-tales-from-the-front-seat.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/cab-tales-from-the-front-seat.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My taxi driver arrived. Valet opened the door for me and I said, &amp;ldquo;Thank you. But I will be sitting in the front.&amp;rdquo; An awkward moment and we were off to explore Chiang Mai, Thailand. What happened next took me by sheer surprise. Why was my driver going ape shit crazy?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A picture is worth a thousand words. Or is it?</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/a-picture-is-worth-a-thousand-words.-or-is-it.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/a-picture-is-worth-a-thousand-words.-or-is-it.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Holding tigers in my arms and playing with them has been on my bucket list for a very long time. And I finally got to experience it at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.tigerkingdom.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The Tiger Kingdom&lt;/a&gt; in Chiang Mai, Thailand. The photos certainly tell  a fun and once in a lifetime experience story. While pictures are worth a thousand words, they don&amp;rsquo;t always tell you the full story. Here&amp;rsquo;s why I regret going to the Tiger Kingdom and the real story behind those pretty pictures.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going against the grain</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/going-against-the-grain.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/going-against-the-grain.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not a big foodie, but holy cowabunga! &lt;a href=&#34;http://grilledcheesegrill.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Grilled Cheese Grill&lt;/a&gt; in Portland, was THAT bloody good. If you&amp;rsquo;ve never experienced food orgasms, then add this to your list in a hurry. Every bite was a bite of heaven. During my first visit, I was impressed with the entire set up, the little details and the experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portland embraces weird</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/portland-embraces-weird.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/portland-embraces-weird.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There are 3 things synonymous in my memory bank when I reminisce about Portland – It&amp;rsquo;s artistic and creative flair, attitude of anything goes which really means, the weirder it is the better, and a very specific type of body odor  that can be used as a deadly weapon to disperse protests instead of using tear gas.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enter the world of Steampunk</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/enter-the-world-of-steampunk.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/enter-the-world-of-steampunk.html.html</guid>
      <description>The beauty of traveling is when you run into the unexpected and new learnings await you. I had such an encounter during my recent travels to Portland, Oregon. I was drawn by an intriguing costume parade taking place in the lobby of the DoubleTree hotel where I was staying. So I followed the costumes. I discovered there was a convention taking place – GearCon 2014. Little did I know, I was about to time travel to an entirely different world!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to beat depression</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/how-to-beat-depression.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/how-to-beat-depression.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Life is tough. No matter your financial status, race, religion, color or gender, we all have our obstacles to overcome. We are all susceptible to fall victim to depression from life altering events like loss of a loved one, mourning the death of a relationship, postpartum depression, miscarriage, bullying, rape, financial woes, divorce, medical problems, disability from an accident, survivors&amp;rsquo; guilt and so on. The list is endless.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can anyone hear me? continued ...</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/can-anyone-hear-me-continued-....html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/can-anyone-hear-me-continued-....html.html</guid>
      <description>To continue our conversation inspired by Robin Williams death and the story I shared &amp;hellip;
There&amp;rsquo;s a school of thought that responds to depression as such – &amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t need anyone else. All you need is you. You need to love yourself and not wait for someone to love you to make you happy.&amp;rdquo; I wholeheartedly agree with this philosophy for people that are not suffering from depression. However, you are not yourself when you are in depression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can anyone hear me?</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/can-anyone-hear-me.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/can-anyone-hear-me.html.html</guid>
      <description>In light of Robin Williams death, it has stirred up a lot of pain within me. It has taken me back down memory lane of my own past dark times. And I&amp;rsquo;ve had a few in my life so far including when I left home (Muscat, Oman) to study in London at the tender age of 15, my divorce and a few others in what seems like fairly recent times. When I look at my own Facebook posts from the years that were tough for me, I can&amp;rsquo;t seem to recognize myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This is India. Uncensored</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/this-is-india.-uncensored.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/this-is-india.-uncensored.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is India &amp;hellip;
Vivid, colorful, historically rich, incredible architecture, vivacious, full of life and energy, majestic, deeply contrasting, sensory overload, heart breaking poverty, mind blowing wealth, beautiful, dirty, luxurious, full of heart and yet so heartless &amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That Mother&#39;s Bond</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/that-mothers-bond.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/that-mothers-bond.html.html</guid>
      <description>This is my all time favorite picture of my Mom with me as it embodies that sacred relationship between a mother and her daughter perfectly.
Let&amp;rsquo;s fast forward several years &amp;hellip; Shortly after my wedding, my marriage started to spiral down the toilet. My heart and mind were at war. I was in a deep depression for one and a half year. So many thoughts and emotions running through my mind – why am I not happy, what changed, why do I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m in prison, can I live like this for the rest of my life, is death better than living like this, what will my family think, what will the Indian society think and how will they treat my family if I pursue a divorce, what happened to the happily ever after and am I a failure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful words of inspiration</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/beautiful-words-of-inspiration.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/beautiful-words-of-inspiration.html.html</guid>
      <description>My brother and I started our company, atmosol, 9 years back. We announced 3 days ago that I have decided to leave atmosol to pursue my new dreams and passion – photography and world travel amongst others. I&amp;rsquo;ve been blown away by the volume and content within the emails, texts, messages on FB/LI and phone calls that I have received. Looks like I may have a few people show up at my funeral in the future after all .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In search of lions ...</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/in-search-of-lions-....html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/in-search-of-lions-....html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s 2 am and the taxi is waiting for us. My relatives and I start our journey from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twiztedmyrtle.photoshelter.com/gallery-collection/View-Gallery/C0000qSXIepKx7lw&#34;&gt;Rajkot&lt;/a&gt; to Gir National Forest, Gujarat, India. We made it there by 5:30am. Phew! A sigh of relief because I wanted to catch the very first morning tour to take some cool shots of the Asiatic Lions against the background of the beautiful morning sunrays.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Story Behind Twizted Myrtle</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/about.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/about.html</guid>
      <description>MAIN IMAGE --             Who the heck are you?  I’m a person.  I’m not brown, black or white. I’m not Indian, Middle-Eastern, British or American. I’m not Hindu, Muslim or Christian. I’m not Democrat or Republican. I’m not heterosexual or homosexual. I’m not man or woman. I’m just a person that’s part of the human race who lives on a tiny planet called Earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When the poor are rich</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/when-the-poor-are-rich.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/when-the-poor-are-rich.html.html</guid>
      <description>This is one of my most cherished photos that left an indelible impression on me. It captures the essence of life and human spirit in more ways than one.
Their home is the median of a very busy main road in Bombay, India. All of their precious belongings are clearly on display that include a battered and probably unhygienic mattress, make shift pillow, clothes and containers. The girl&amp;rsquo;s right leg is on the street with cars narrowly scraping by her, drivers are honking and inching through the chaos, bikers are anxiously seeking an opening so they can zip through traffic, people are jay walking, street vendors are hustling with their customers &amp;hellip; the noise is unbearable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flying tree to tree</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/flying-tree-to-tree.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/flying-tree-to-tree.html.html</guid>
      <description>It was impossible to resist The Flying Hanuman, a thrilling zip lining eco adventure in Phuket, Thailand.
Our party of 8 got suited up. The stench of hundreds of people&amp;rsquo;s body odor was living and breathing within the gear. I was thankful to know that my gag reflexes were in good working order . And like a dummy, I innocently and confidently asked one of the guides if they had febreze.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magical Islands in Phuket</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/magical-islands-in-phuket.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/magical-islands-in-phuket.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.johngray-seacanoe.com/index.php&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;John Gray Sea Canoe&lt;/a&gt; tour in Phuket, Thailand, took me by surprise. I expected to see some cool sea caves, hundreds of bats huddled at the top of the cave ceilings, enjoy a little kayaking, appreciate nature&amp;rsquo;s beauty, take a few photos to remember the day and head back to the hotel. While all that came true, we experienced something so much more magical than that.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joy through others</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/joy-through-others.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/joy-through-others.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After capturing the peacock shot at Aji Dam (see &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/posts/why-so-special.html&#34;&gt;Why so special?&lt;/a&gt;, we weren&amp;rsquo;t ready to go home just yet. We drove around the city as it was slowly waking up and to see what else we could stumble upon.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why so special?</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/why-so-special.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/why-so-special.html.html</guid>
      <description>While this may not be the sharpest photo in my collection, it is very dear to me because of what it signifies for my journey in photography. Here&amp;rsquo;s the back story &amp;hellip;
Two of my cousins in Rajkot, India, entertained my madness by actually waking up super early in the morning to take me to Aji Dam for some cool sunrise shots. Pitch black and off we went. The roads were clear, silent and peaceful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello world!</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/hello-world.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/hello-world.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Photography is so much about perspective. Photos convey one aspect of the truth, but not always the entire truth or reality. There just may be another side to the story.  As I have discovered this through my photography, I have fallen in love with this art even more.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>