<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Podcasts on Twizted Myrtle</title>
    <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Podcasts on Twizted Myrtle</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>When Fashion Is Murder</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/when-fashion-is-murder.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/when-fashion-is-murder.html.html</guid>
      <description>Compassionate or Murderer - What statement do your fashion choices make about you?
Our desire for comfort and to look cool in fur coats, leather handbags and snakeskin shoes comes at an unthinkable price; cows, dogs and cats are amongst the many animals that are subjected to heart wrenching cruelty. How is that cool? What really happens behind the scenes? How can India be the biggest supplier of cows for the leather industry when they consider cows to be sacred?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Legalize or Not to Legalize Marijuana, with Doug Coleman, Special Agent at Drug Enforcement Agency</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/to-legalize-or-not-to-legalize-marijuana-with-doug-coleman-special-agent-at-drug-enforcement-agency.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/to-legalize-or-not-to-legalize-marijuana-with-doug-coleman-special-agent-at-drug-enforcement-agency.html.html</guid>
      <description>Doug Coleman is a 25-year veteran and Special Agent for DEA, in charge of the Phoenix Field Division, and Michael Pooley, Metro Operations Lieutenant for Tempe Police Department. As a border state, Arizona plays a vital role in the infiltration and distribution of drugs to the rest of our country. We engage in a riveting conversation about all things drugs, no holds barred!
Do DEA agents have any compassion for drug dealers and the choices they make as a result of their circumstances?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Louie Psihoyos, Academy Award Winning Director, Creates the Tipping Point to Change the World!</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/how-louie-psihoyos-academy-award-winning-director-creates-the-tipping-point-to-change-the-world.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/how-louie-psihoyos-academy-award-winning-director-creates-the-tipping-point-to-change-the-world.html.html</guid>
      <description>Louie Psihoyos is an Academy Award Winning Director, and Founder/CEO of Oceanic Preservation Society. With a three day crash course in film making, it&amp;rsquo;s ironic that Louie&amp;rsquo;s first documentary film, The Cove, won over 100 awards including the Academy Award. How is this even possible? What advice did Steven Spielberg give him? Did he listen? Louie discusses how covert operations allowed him to capture one of the most poignant and chilling scenes in The Cove, where elders in Taiji, Japan, share how they used to kill Blue Whales prior to wreaking havoc on dolphins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Behind the Scenes with Nyla, an Extraordinaire Burlesque Stripper</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/behind-the-scenes-with-nyla-an-extraordinaire-burlesque-stripper.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/behind-the-scenes-with-nyla-an-extraordinaire-burlesque-stripper.html.html</guid>
      <description>What does a man REALLY want when he goes to a strip club? Nyla, founder of Violet Flame Studios, and an extraordinaire Burlesque Stripper, takes us behind the scenes and unveils how strip clubs work, stripper code of ethics and the art of seduction. But how did she make the big leap from being a dancer to a stripper? What was it like when she got topless for the first time?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pt 2 - Adam Sud, Former Addict&#39;s Perspective on How to Get Through to an Addict and The War on Drugs</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-2---adam-sud-former-addicts-perspective-on-how-to-get-through-to-an-addict-and-the-war-on-drugs.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-2---adam-sud-former-addicts-perspective-on-how-to-get-through-to-an-addict-and-the-war-on-drugs.html.html</guid>
      <description>Adam Sud is the son of one of the founding investors of Whole Foods. Despite having all the right ingredients in life, Adam’s life was on the fastest route to self destruction. But Adam took charge and reversed his Type 2 Diabetes, lost 150lbs, kicked his addiction to Adderall and Food … and transformed his life … physically, as well as emotionally. In our last episode, Adam shared the journey of his transformation and what he lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pt 1 - How Adam Sud Reversed His Diabetes, Lost 150 lbs, Kicked His Food/Rx Addiction and Transformed His Life</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-1---how-adam-sud-reversed-his-diabetes-lost-150-lbs-kicked-his-food/rx-addiction-and-transformed-his-life.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-1---how-adam-sud-reversed-his-diabetes-lost-150-lbs-kicked-his-food/rx-addiction-and-transformed-his-life.html.html</guid>
      <description>Adam Sud is the son of founding investor of Whole Foods. Despite having access to all the right ingredients in life, Adam found himself addicted to prescription drugs, overweight at 300 lbs, diagnosed with Type 2 Diabetes, low self esteem, wrapped in depression and anger, out of cash, unemployed and primed to live on the streets? How? And why? Adam went from a journey of self-destruction to inspiring self-transformation. Adam reversed his Type 2 Diabetes, lost 150 lbs, gained his self esteem and emotional health back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life After “The Last Letter” by Marc Lee, an American Decorated Fallen Hero</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/life-after-the-last-letter-by-marc-lee-an-american-decorated-fallen-hero.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/life-after-the-last-letter-by-marc-lee-an-american-decorated-fallen-hero.html.html</guid>
      <description>Knock. Knock. Your son, Marc Lee, has been killed in action. As a parent, losing your child is the most painful, heart wrenching and unnatural thing to experience. How do you even process this? How do you deal with such depths of pain and grief? Can you ever heal from such a devastating loss? How do you go on? We talk to Debbie Lee, Marc’s Mom, to discuss this difficult and inspiring journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pt 2 - ISIS &amp; Mind Control: Looking at Suicide Bombers Through a Different Lens</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-2---isis--mind-control-looking-at-suicide-bombers-through-a-different-lens.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-2---isis--mind-control-looking-at-suicide-bombers-through-a-different-lens.html.html</guid>
      <description>Are suicide bombers and members of terrorist groups like ISIS and Al Qaeda demons or are they victims themselves? What does the future hold for young children who have been brainswashed by ISIS? Can and how can people that have been in cult groups for decades be deprogrammed successfully? Will Tom Cruise ever be able to get out of Scientology? Rick Ross, an expert on destructive cults, shares valuable insights into this other world and the process of deprogramming minds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pt 1 - Can Anyone Succumb to Cults and Brainwashing?</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-1---can-anyone-succumb-to-cults-and-brainwashing.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-1---can-anyone-succumb-to-cults-and-brainwashing.html.html</guid>
      <description>Rick Ross is the founder and Executive Director of The Cult Education Institute. He is an internationally known expert on destructive cults, controversial groups and movements. Rick helps us understand if there is a particular profile of people that are more susceptible to cults. How does a cult leader disable our ability to think independently and rationally? What are the exit costs of leaving a cult group? How is Catholicism or Mormonism different from Scientology?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Real Truth Behind Men, Sex and How They Think</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/the-real-truth-behind-men-sex-and-how-they-think.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/the-real-truth-behind-men-sex-and-how-they-think.html.html</guid>
      <description>Vince Kelvin is a famous seduction coach. As a pick up artist, he teaches men how to seduce women and get them in the sack. Sickening, right? Or so it would seem at first glance. Vince opens up about his own personal journey into how be became a pick up artist. His &amp;ldquo;artistry&amp;rdquo; was featured in Lisa Ling&amp;rsquo;s documentary &amp;ldquo;This Is Life&amp;rdquo; on CNN. How does he feel about love, marriage and relationships?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pratham USA, Breaking The Cycle of Poverty and Illiteracy in India</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pratham-usa-breaking-the-cycle-of-poverty-and-illiteracy-in-india.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pratham-usa-breaking-the-cycle-of-poverty-and-illiteracy-in-india.html.html</guid>
      <description>Meet Amit Shah. Education and poverty strike a very personal chord for him. His passion for education turned into action when he got involved with Pratham USA, as a Board Member. Pratham is a non profit organization that strives to educate 200 million children in India that currently cannot read or write. How is that even possible when India boasts 96% enrollment of children in schools? Amit shares his experiences and insights in the lives of some of the children from low income families – what their daily lives look like, daily struggles, their dreams and aspirations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time to Reconsider &#39;Stranger Danger&#39; Teachings and Rethink Concept of Trust</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/time-to-reconsider-stranger-danger-teachings-and-rethink-concept-of-trust.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/time-to-reconsider-stranger-danger-teachings-and-rethink-concept-of-trust.html.html</guid>
      <description>Kids are sexually abused mostly by people in our trusted circle - friends, relatives, teachers and priests. So isn&amp;rsquo;t it time to reconsider &amp;ldquo;Stranger Danger?&amp;rdquo; If we can&amp;rsquo;t trust our family and friends, then who can we trust? Michael Pooley, Lieutenant and PIO at Tempe Police Department, and Rachel Lutowsky, Founder of Dynamic Leadership, and parents, share new and noteworthy insights on what to teach your children so they don&amp;rsquo;t become victims.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Divorce or Stay Unhappily Married for Kids, Society and Culture?</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/divorce-or-stay-unhappily-married-for-kids-society-and-culture.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/divorce-or-stay-unhappily-married-for-kids-society-and-culture.html.html</guid>
      <description>How many unhappy people do you know that stay married for the sake of their kids? Or because even thinking of divorce is taboo in your culture? Should you dare? Does divorce make you a selfish person? Nitin, Indian, was married for 18 years. He shares what he experienced in his marriage, why he considered divorce and how that has impacted his son.
Listen to Show

Resources -
 What You Don&amp;rsquo;t Know About Marriage The inconvenient truth about love - and divorce -  Four Patterns That Predict Divorce (part 1) The Impact of Divorce on Children Deciding to Divorce?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pt 2 - Racing Extinction - Why The Time to Act Is NOW!</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-2---racing-extinction---why-the-time-to-act-is-now.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-2---racing-extinction---why-the-time-to-act-is-now.html.html</guid>
      <description>Shawn Heinrichs - Our conversation continues with Shawn, an Emmy Winning Award Winning Cinematographer, artist, photographer and marine conservationist. It&amp;rsquo;s an awakening, inspiring &amp;amp; intellectually stimulating conversation. Why do people choose to believe that they, as one person, cannot make a difference? Why is the fishing industry knowingly leading creatures to extinction and the death of their livelihood? What does Shawn think of humanity? And behind the scenes on some of the moments showcased in the documentary film, Racing Extinction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pt 1 - Can One Person Change The World?</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-1---can-one-person-change-the-world.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-1---can-one-person-change-the-world.html.html</guid>
      <description>Shawn Heinrichs, an Emmy Award Winning Cinematographer, artist, photographer, and Shark and Manta Ray Defender. Or, more accurately, a Real Life Avenger! Shawn’s incredibly moving work was recently featured in the documentary film, Racing Extinction. But what inspired him to transform his life from corporate America to dedicating and risking his life to save Sharks and Manta Rays? Can one man really change the world?
Listen to Show

Resources -</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to stop living in fear? - Joe Bailey, psychologist, author and speaker</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/how-to-stop-living-in-fear---joe-bailey-psychologist-author-and-speaker.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/how-to-stop-living-in-fear---joe-bailey-psychologist-author-and-speaker.html.html</guid>
      <description>Do you live everyday in fear and anxiety? Does media play a role in the fear with which we live our lives? ISIS. Ebola. Earthquake … the list goes on. How about living in fear due to our own personal experiences and thoughts? Or Donald Trump (and Cruz)? Joe Bailey, psychologist, author and speaker, discuss where fear comes from, why we respond to it and how we can fearproof our lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Do Pakistanis and Indians hate each other?</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/why-do-pakistanis-and-indians-hate-each-other.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/why-do-pakistanis-and-indians-hate-each-other.html.html</guid>
      <description>Why do Pakistanis and Indians hate each other? How does a child pick up on these social and historical cues? Personally, I hated Pakistanis as I was growing up. Do we have good reason to hate each other? What role does Patriotism and cricket play in fueling this hatred? Mustapha, Pakistani, who married an Indian girl, shares his experiences and insight into this issue.
Listen to Show

Resources
 India - Pakistan Relations India - Pakistan Cricket Rivalry A rivalry that threatens the world India-Pakistan Relations: A Destructive Equilibrium Movie - Gandhi  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How NOT to become a victim to your financial advisor with Tigran</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/how-not-to-become-a-victim-to-your-financial-advisor-with-tigran.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/how-not-to-become-a-victim-to-your-financial-advisor-with-tigran.html.html</guid>
      <description>Ever had a bad experience with a financial advisor or know someone who did? Are you afraid of being a victim to these shady advisors? My financial advisor, and friend, certainly helped me lose thousands of dollars. Sadly, this is a fairly common occurrence. Are you trying to get back in the game, but don&amp;rsquo;t know how? Tigran from Hatton Consulting shares insights into the financial industry so you can avoid the pitfalls and get back in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Growing up Black in Chicago with Gina</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/growing-up-black-in-chicago-with-gina.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/growing-up-black-in-chicago-with-gina.html.html</guid>
      <description>Does every Black person experience racial discrimination? Do we need more Black role models? Why do kids wear their pants down? We discuss this and all things Black with Gina who grew up in Chicago in the 1970s.
Listen to Show</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pt 2 - How being an entrepreneur can impact personal relationships with Josh Carroll</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-2---how-being-an-entrepreneur-can-impact-personal-relationships-with-josh-carroll.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-2---how-being-an-entrepreneur-can-impact-personal-relationships-with-josh-carroll.html.html</guid>
      <description>Being an entrepreneur sounds glamorous. But there is a dark underbelly to being a business owner. Josh Carroll, COO &amp;amp; Co-Founder of endsight, shares raw insights into how his entrepreneurial journey impacted his relationship with his wife. Their glamorous life had it all – bankruptcy, post partum depression, fights, dysfunctional love, bitterness and so much more. How did they sort through so much baggage?
Listen to Show</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pt 1 - What it&#39;s REALLY like to be an entrepreneur with Josh Carroll</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-1---what-its-really-like-to-be-an-entrepreneur-with-josh-carroll.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/pt-1---what-its-really-like-to-be-an-entrepreneur-with-josh-carroll.html.html</guid>
      <description>Rarely do you hear true and uncensored stories about what it&amp;rsquo;s REALLY like to be an entrepreneur. To most, owning your own company means you&amp;rsquo;re rolling in a pile of Benjamins and life is peachy. Josh Carroll, COO &amp;amp; Co-Founder of endsight, shares openly and with refreshing honesty about the “real” story behind his entrepreneurial success.
Listen to Show

Resources -
 Inc. Article - The Psychological Price of Entrepreneurship  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India’s obsession with white skin</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/indias-obsession-with-white-skin.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/indias-obsession-with-white-skin.html.html</guid>
      <description>You think America has problems with skin color? Try India! Did you know that India is obsessed with white skin. What are the implications of this unhealthy desire for fair skin? How does this translate into society … our thoughts, self worth and interactions? We explore this topic in depth with Suhrid Ganguly, a Bengali, who has a darker skin complexion.
Listen to Show

Resources -
 Doll Test Video Dark Girls Documentary BBC - “Racist” Thailand skin-whitening advert is withdrawn  Manipulative messages by Fair and Lovely Commercial  Bollywood Actresses like Priyanka Chopra that have undergone skin lightening treatment BBC - Africa, where black is not really beautiful When Black Teens get real about America’s love of light skin BBC - #unfairandlovely: A new social campaign celebrates dark skin   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sexual Advances in Business</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/sexual-advances-in-business.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/sexual-advances-in-business.html.html</guid>
      <description>As a working woman, do you struggle with men hitting on you in business settings? Have you figured out how to handle these unwanted sexual advances, while being taken seriously for your work? Rachel Lutowsky, founder of Dynamic Leadership Solutions, shares some of her undesired experiences and what she’s learned from them.
As a working man, you may also want to tune in to listen to what women experience in the workplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do you know you’re gay?</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/how-do-you-know-youre-gay.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/how-do-you-know-youre-gay.html.html</guid>
      <description>Jeffrey Hattrick was born in a conservative Catholic family. He found himself attracted to men. Oh Boy! So how did his parents react when a love letter he wrote to his man crush fell out of his bag? How did he handle being shoved in trash cans in school? Is it okay to call someone gay, queer or fag? Do gay people have the desire to have children? How do gay people have sex?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Len’s heart attack “woke” him up from a life of quiet desperation</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/how-lens-heart-attack-woke-him-up-from-a-life-of-quiet-desperation.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/how-lens-heart-attack-woke-him-up-from-a-life-of-quiet-desperation.html.html</guid>
      <description>Are you living a life of quiet desperation? You know you’re not happy, but don’t know how to get out of it? Len Gutman knows what that’s like. It took a heart attack to wake him up and change the course of his life. His journey led him to discovering true happiness.
Here’s how he did it - Listen to Show

Resources -
 American Heart Association - www.heart.org Heart Attack Support Group - Under 55 heartattack Calcium Test - Coronary Calcium Scan Book - How to find fulfilling work, Roman Krznaric Book - Your money or your life, Vicki Robin and Joe Dominguez  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sara’s journey of sexual abuse, self-injury and drug addiction</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/saras-journey-of-sexual-abuse-self-injury-and-drug-addiction.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/podcast/saras-journey-of-sexual-abuse-self-injury-and-drug-addiction.html.html</guid>
      <description>Meet Sara. It would be fair to say that she&amp;rsquo;s been through hell and back. Sara sheds light on how her perpetrator groomed her for one year to become a victim of sexual abuse. How did he get in her mind? What drove her to cut her body with a razor and become addicted to it? How did she get introduced to drugs?
Her reasons were profound! She left me speechless.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>