<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Twizted Myrtle</title>
    <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Twizted Myrtle</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>You Complete Me</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/you-complete-me.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/you-complete-me.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Romantic words that make your heart flutter, and arguably, the biggest crock of shit ever vocalized as the Holy Grail in the name of love! So what do these words really mean? Let the indulgence begin …&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twizted New Year</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/twizted-new-year.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/twizted-new-year.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Every year we wish for peace and happiness. So why have we not attained it yet? We can achieve the unthinkable like landing man on the moon when we have collective undeterred resolve. And yet, peace continues to evade us.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Giving</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/the-art-of-giving.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/the-art-of-giving.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Why do we give gifts? Consciously or sub-consciously and to varying degrees, we use gifts as a way to further our agenda – impress or pacify someone, fulfill an obligation, win them over, one-up the recipient or our competition, score points , call in a favor in the future, use as a tool for guilt and manipulation, earn bragging rights or boost our own ego. When we give with ulterior motives, agenda or expectations, a gift turns into a contract.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chasing Unhappiness</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/chasing-unhappiness.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/chasing-unhappiness.html.html</guid>
      <description>While lazing around on a Sunday afternoon, my mind, like most entrepreneurs, was working. In doing so, I asked myself one question – The day you reach the heights of success you’ve always envisioned for your company (my BHAG – Big Hairy Audacious Goal), how will you feel that day? The answer surprised me – Emptiness.
While I would feel a strong sense of accomplishment, proud of our team and what we built together, I also became acutely aware that it would be a shallow experience; I would feel a deep sense of emptiness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Majestic Close Encounter</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/a-majestic-close-encounter.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/a-majestic-close-encounter.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Whales are majestic creatures that symbolize freedom. They can make hearts palpitate with giddiness and excitement like teenage romance. So imagine the inner screams when the Captain radioed our Zodiac driver, Christophe, that there is a whale by the ship and is putting on quite the show. Okay, let&amp;rsquo;s back up a little.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decision to ban India&#39;s Daughter</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/decision-to-ban-indias-daughter.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/decision-to-ban-indias-daughter.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Outcry over the documentary, India&amp;rsquo;s daughter, led to a swift response by the government. The government and parts of the community that supported the decision to ban the documentary is very telling of the Indian mentality  and is worth a closer look.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experiencing Aurora Borealis</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/experiencing-aurora-borealis.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/experiencing-aurora-borealis.html.html</guid>
      <description>Last year, the temptation to see Aurora Borealis grew beyond being a number on my bucket list. I could not resist anymore. So I booked my trip to Iceland for two weeks in December. My excitement came crashing down when my friend educated me that seeing Aurora Borealis is not guaranteed. It&amp;rsquo;s a matter of right weather conditions and location within the country. So off I went to Iceland, with more realistic expectations while hoping to get lucky.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspirational Traveling Mom</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/inspirational-traveling-mom.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/inspirational-traveling-mom.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;New Year&amp;rsquo;s Resolutions are a running joke. They fizzle away by mid-February each year. And yet, we keep repeating the cycle. We have good reasons like our husband, wife, children, job, money and time that keep getting in the way. But the truth is they are not our reasons; they are our excuses.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three hardest words to say</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/three-hardest-words-to-say.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/three-hardest-words-to-say.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Several years ago, if you told me to say &amp;ldquo;I love you&amp;rdquo; to my parents or siblings, I would have laughed and brushed you off. The mere thought of verbalizing such emotional words that made me feel so exposed and vulnerable  was screechingly uncomfortable. We all knew that we loved and cared for each other deeply; but we never actually uttered those three tough words. Never!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iceland, my worst nightmare transformed</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/iceland-my-worst-nightmare-transformed.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/iceland-my-worst-nightmare-transformed.html.html</guid>
      <description>Iceland is unique, complex and intriguing. The island is transforming and evolving in real time since it is geologically active. It is a land of many volcanoes, geysers, geothermal springs, black sand beach , moss and lava fields, mountains, glaciers, lakes, fjords and aurora borealis. I was sold. So I booked a 14-day trip for December, which included a 7-day photo tour with the talented photographer, Iurie Belegurschi. As December approached, I was hardly able to contain my excitement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons learned in 2014</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/lessons-learned-in-2014.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/lessons-learned-in-2014.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just as every book has an end, I conclude each year of my life by reflecting on the big lessons learned that year. In this process, one thing has been consistent since I was thirteen. Each year I look back and realize  how ignorant, immature and daft I was the year prior. In that respect, I love growing old and hopefully a penny wiser. Click below to read the full article:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rethink Respect  |  7 lessons learned from celebrity rapists</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/rethink-respect----7-lessons-learned-from-celebrity-rapists.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/rethink-respect----7-lessons-learned-from-celebrity-rapists.html.html</guid>
      <description>Could Bill Cosby, the most respected family man and Father of America have raped 15 women and counting? That just cannot be. Right? Parents and children equally looked up to him; parents wanted to emulate him and children wanted a father like him. He was wise, funny, educated, understanding, and just plain cool! He was well respected, both as Bill Cosby and as Dr. Huxtable. And that&amp;rsquo;s exactly where it all goes wrong — Respect and Reputation!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First timers guide to Cruise Vacations</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/first-timers-guide-to-cruise-vacations.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/first-timers-guide-to-cruise-vacations.html.html</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve traveled the world by plane, train, bus and car, but never a cruise. The concept of being stuck in a finite amount of space never seemed appealing to me. Still, I wanted to experience it first hand and decide how I really felt about cruise vacations. So in July 2010, I booked a 7 day Mexican Riviera Cruise on the Royal Caribbean, Mariner of the Seas, for our family vacation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coach Needs Coaching In Customer Service!</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/coach-needs-coaching-in-customer-service.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/coach-needs-coaching-in-customer-service.html.html</guid>
      <description>This story makes my blood boil on many levels – as an entrepreneur, as someone who has been on both sides of customer service, as a daughter and as a person. How does spilling a drink on the floor, a trivial event, translate into the most heinous crime of this century? Assistant manager leads her posse by example – arrogance, ego, disrespect and lack of common courtesy. But was this an isolated incident?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I was high ... on speed!</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/i-was-high-...-on-speed.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/i-was-high-...-on-speed.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was a beautiful morning on Dec 7&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt;, 2012 and I was headed out for &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bondurant.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bondurant High Performance Driving School&lt;/a&gt;. The wait for this day had been too long. I had finally signed up for their one-day course which was jam-packed with learning driving maneuvers, techniques and track time. I was super excited, nervous and slightly intimidated. But mostly, I could not contain myself!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women want equality. But only when we want it.</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/women-want-equality.-but-only-when-we-want-it..html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/women-want-equality.-but-only-when-we-want-it..html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Consider a business lunch meeting, date night or just hanging out with friends. Waiter brings the check and typically drops it off closer to the man. Ignoring that gender bias for a hot second, who do you think should pay?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Human Zoo</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/the-human-zoo.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/the-human-zoo.html.html</guid>
      <description>After my experience at The Tiger Kingdom, I was on my way to the next hot spot – The Long Neck Tribe Village in Chiang Mai, Thailand, which came with high recommendations. My expectation was that I was going to be able to visit, interact and learn about The Long Neck Tribe people, culture and their way of life, with authenticity. Little did I know, I was actually visiting a human zoo, where The Long Neck Tribe people were on display for me to gawk at.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cab tales from the front seat</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/cab-tales-from-the-front-seat.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/cab-tales-from-the-front-seat.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My taxi driver arrived. Valet opened the door for me and I said, &amp;ldquo;Thank you. But I will be sitting in the front.&amp;rdquo; An awkward moment and we were off to explore Chiang Mai, Thailand. What happened next took me by sheer surprise. Why was my driver going ape shit crazy?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A picture is worth a thousand words. Or is it?</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/a-picture-is-worth-a-thousand-words.-or-is-it.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/a-picture-is-worth-a-thousand-words.-or-is-it.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Holding tigers in my arms and playing with them has been on my bucket list for a very long time. And I finally got to experience it at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.tigerkingdom.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The Tiger Kingdom&lt;/a&gt; in Chiang Mai, Thailand. The photos certainly tell  a fun and once in a lifetime experience story. While pictures are worth a thousand words, they don&amp;rsquo;t always tell you the full story. Here&amp;rsquo;s why I regret going to the Tiger Kingdom and the real story behind those pretty pictures.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going against the grain</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/going-against-the-grain.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/going-against-the-grain.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not a big foodie, but holy cowabunga! &lt;a href=&#34;http://grilledcheesegrill.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Grilled Cheese Grill&lt;/a&gt; in Portland, was THAT bloody good. If you&amp;rsquo;ve never experienced food orgasms, then add this to your list in a hurry. Every bite was a bite of heaven. During my first visit, I was impressed with the entire set up, the little details and the experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portland embraces weird</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/portland-embraces-weird.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/portland-embraces-weird.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There are 3 things synonymous in my memory bank when I reminisce about Portland – It&amp;rsquo;s artistic and creative flair, attitude of anything goes which really means, the weirder it is the better, and a very specific type of body odor  that can be used as a deadly weapon to disperse protests instead of using tear gas.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enter the world of Steampunk</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/enter-the-world-of-steampunk.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/enter-the-world-of-steampunk.html.html</guid>
      <description>The beauty of traveling is when you run into the unexpected and new learnings await you. I had such an encounter during my recent travels to Portland, Oregon. I was drawn by an intriguing costume parade taking place in the lobby of the DoubleTree hotel where I was staying. So I followed the costumes. I discovered there was a convention taking place – GearCon 2014. Little did I know, I was about to time travel to an entirely different world!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to beat depression</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/how-to-beat-depression.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/how-to-beat-depression.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Life is tough. No matter your financial status, race, religion, color or gender, we all have our obstacles to overcome. We are all susceptible to fall victim to depression from life altering events like loss of a loved one, mourning the death of a relationship, postpartum depression, miscarriage, bullying, rape, financial woes, divorce, medical problems, disability from an accident, survivors&amp;rsquo; guilt and so on. The list is endless.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can anyone hear me? continued ...</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/can-anyone-hear-me-continued-....html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/can-anyone-hear-me-continued-....html.html</guid>
      <description>To continue our conversation inspired by Robin Williams death and the story I shared &amp;hellip;
There&amp;rsquo;s a school of thought that responds to depression as such – &amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t need anyone else. All you need is you. You need to love yourself and not wait for someone to love you to make you happy.&amp;rdquo; I wholeheartedly agree with this philosophy for people that are not suffering from depression. However, you are not yourself when you are in depression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can anyone hear me?</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/can-anyone-hear-me.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/can-anyone-hear-me.html.html</guid>
      <description>In light of Robin Williams death, it has stirred up a lot of pain within me. It has taken me back down memory lane of my own past dark times. And I&amp;rsquo;ve had a few in my life so far including when I left home (Muscat, Oman) to study in London at the tender age of 15, my divorce and a few others in what seems like fairly recent times. When I look at my own Facebook posts from the years that were tough for me, I can&amp;rsquo;t seem to recognize myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This is India. Uncensored</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/this-is-india.-uncensored.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/this-is-india.-uncensored.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is India &amp;hellip;
Vivid, colorful, historically rich, incredible architecture, vivacious, full of life and energy, majestic, deeply contrasting, sensory overload, heart breaking poverty, mind blowing wealth, beautiful, dirty, luxurious, full of heart and yet so heartless &amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That Mother&#39;s Bond</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/that-mothers-bond.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/that-mothers-bond.html.html</guid>
      <description>This is my all time favorite picture of my Mom with me as it embodies that sacred relationship between a mother and her daughter perfectly.
Let&amp;rsquo;s fast forward several years &amp;hellip; Shortly after my wedding, my marriage started to spiral down the toilet. My heart and mind were at war. I was in a deep depression for one and a half year. So many thoughts and emotions running through my mind – why am I not happy, what changed, why do I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m in prison, can I live like this for the rest of my life, is death better than living like this, what will my family think, what will the Indian society think and how will they treat my family if I pursue a divorce, what happened to the happily ever after and am I a failure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful words of inspiration</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/beautiful-words-of-inspiration.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/beautiful-words-of-inspiration.html.html</guid>
      <description>My brother and I started our company, atmosol, 9 years back. We announced 3 days ago that I have decided to leave atmosol to pursue my new dreams and passion – photography and world travel amongst others. I&amp;rsquo;ve been blown away by the volume and content within the emails, texts, messages on FB/LI and phone calls that I have received. Looks like I may have a few people show up at my funeral in the future after all .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In search of lions ...</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/in-search-of-lions-....html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/in-search-of-lions-....html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s 2 am and the taxi is waiting for us. My relatives and I start our journey from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twiztedmyrtle.photoshelter.com/gallery-collection/View-Gallery/C0000qSXIepKx7lw&#34;&gt;Rajkot&lt;/a&gt; to Gir National Forest, Gujarat, India. We made it there by 5:30am. Phew! A sigh of relief because I wanted to catch the very first morning tour to take some cool shots of the Asiatic Lions against the background of the beautiful morning sunrays.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When the poor are rich</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/when-the-poor-are-rich.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/when-the-poor-are-rich.html.html</guid>
      <description>This is one of my most cherished photos that left an indelible impression on me. It captures the essence of life and human spirit in more ways than one.
Their home is the median of a very busy main road in Bombay, India. All of their precious belongings are clearly on display that include a battered and probably unhygienic mattress, make shift pillow, clothes and containers. The girl&amp;rsquo;s right leg is on the street with cars narrowly scraping by her, drivers are honking and inching through the chaos, bikers are anxiously seeking an opening so they can zip through traffic, people are jay walking, street vendors are hustling with their customers &amp;hellip; the noise is unbearable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flying tree to tree</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/flying-tree-to-tree.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/flying-tree-to-tree.html.html</guid>
      <description>It was impossible to resist The Flying Hanuman, a thrilling zip lining eco adventure in Phuket, Thailand.
Our party of 8 got suited up. The stench of hundreds of people&amp;rsquo;s body odor was living and breathing within the gear. I was thankful to know that my gag reflexes were in good working order . And like a dummy, I innocently and confidently asked one of the guides if they had febreze.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magical Islands in Phuket</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/magical-islands-in-phuket.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/magical-islands-in-phuket.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.johngray-seacanoe.com/index.php&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;John Gray Sea Canoe&lt;/a&gt; tour in Phuket, Thailand, took me by surprise. I expected to see some cool sea caves, hundreds of bats huddled at the top of the cave ceilings, enjoy a little kayaking, appreciate nature&amp;rsquo;s beauty, take a few photos to remember the day and head back to the hotel. While all that came true, we experienced something so much more magical than that.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joy through others</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/joy-through-others.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/joy-through-others.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After capturing the peacock shot at Aji Dam (see &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/posts/why-so-special.html&#34;&gt;Why so special?&lt;/a&gt;, we weren&amp;rsquo;t ready to go home just yet. We drove around the city as it was slowly waking up and to see what else we could stumble upon.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why so special?</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/why-so-special.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/why-so-special.html.html</guid>
      <description>While this may not be the sharpest photo in my collection, it is very dear to me because of what it signifies for my journey in photography. Here&amp;rsquo;s the back story &amp;hellip;
Two of my cousins in Rajkot, India, entertained my madness by actually waking up super early in the morning to take me to Aji Dam for some cool sunrise shots. Pitch black and off we went. The roads were clear, silent and peaceful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello world!</title>
      <link>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/hello-world.html.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://twiztedmyrtle.github.io/blog/hello-world.html.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Photography is so much about perspective. Photos convey one aspect of the truth, but not always the entire truth or reality. There just may be another side to the story.  As I have discovered this through my photography, I have fallen in love with this art even more.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>